Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
  - Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1959
    - Sub-Series 1. General Correspondence, 1959
      - Fur & Leather - Special Sub-Committee, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 46)
        Minutes including reports of officers on organization drives
      - Misc. D-E-F, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 47)
        To Albert Feldman re dispute at Bucks County Fur Products; Fashion Institute of Technology correspondence
      - Hollanderizing, Local 88, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 48-49)
        Correspondence re arbitration; legal documents re arbitration with A.M.C.
      - Inter-Office Correspondence, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 50)
        Requesting various reports and contract information
      - Israel Histadrut, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 51)
        Address by the Hon. Armand D'Angelo Commissioner for the Dept. of Water Supply, Gas & Electricity at the Installation Dinner for American Trade Union Council for Histadrut re Israel; remarks by Mitchell Sviridoff, President Connecticut State Labor Council
      - Misc. G-H-I, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 52)
        ILGWU sponsored cooperative housing project; institutional growth fund share purchases
      - Joint Board Biennial Convention, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 53-54)
        Report on activities since last convention & present contract negotiations; welfare and retirement funds; proposed amended by-laws (Fur Dresses); routine convention material
      - Joint Board Conference, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 55)
        List of delegates, invitations; activities since last conference (same as in convention folder); address by Harold Cammer - report on conference
      - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959 (Box 15, Folder 56)
        Book of Law; summary of new law by Cammer & Shapiro; law published by A.M.C.& B.W. of N.A.
      - Legislation - City, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 57)
      - Legislation - Federal, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 58)
        Support of Senate Resolution 96 (curtailment of nuclear testing)
      - Liberal Party, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        Trade union council letters; invitations to liberal party meetings
      - Miscellaneous J-L, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        Short bio data for Myer Klig
      - Minutes of sub council meetings, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        May 9-10, 1959
      - Miscellaneous - Routine, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Montreal Fur Workers, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        Collective bargaining procedure; piece work rates; Acadia Fur organizing drive; minutes of Canadian Conference of the Fur & Leather Department; settlement between Fur Workers Union and Fur Dressers & Dyers; Photo of the Fur Industry Parity Committee, Jan.
      - Mouton Price Lists, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        Piece work rates for shops; notes from employers conference
      - Non communists affidavits, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
      - Organizers Reports, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - M-O Misc., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Photos, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        3 unidentified photos; 1 entitled presentation charter for salesmen guild
      - Promotional campaign, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 12)
        invitation to promotional conference; pre-conference correspondence; minutes of Fur Industry Promotion Bureau Executive Committee; resolutions adopted at Fur Industry meeting
      - Promotional Campaign, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
        Fur topics - newspaper of the fur information and fashion council; photos of the young designers collection part of the PR package; PR packages put together by Ruder & Finn - targeting certain age groups; correspondence re fur campaign; photos for the You
      - Promotional campaign, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 15)
        Press releases; newspaper clippings; photos of the Young in Furs collection
      - Promotional campaign, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
        Photos of the Young Designers collection
      - Promotional campaign, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 17)
        Fur Topics: Newspaper of the Fur Info & Fashion Council; PR material; Ruder & Finn annual review
      - Promotional campaign, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 18)
        Press releases; newspaper clippings
      - Publications - Misc., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Reports, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 20)
        Employers' Conference - Mouton
      - Taft Hartley Compliance, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 21)
        Non-Communist Affidavits; financial statements; various certificates from NLRB; P-Q-R Misc.; general correspondence
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, legal papers, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, legal papers, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 48, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 48, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 64, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 80, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 88, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 150, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 150, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Taft Hartley Compliance Joint Board, Local 165, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - U.S. Tariff, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 32)
        Report on Escape - Clause Investigation No.79 under 87 of trade agreement; mink skins from the United States Tariff Commission
      - S-T-U Misc., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 33)
        Requested resignation of Sam Singer as Trustee
      - White Lake Lodge, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 34)
        Correspondence re the financial transactions between Hebrew Institute & union
      - Y-Z correspondence, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 35)
        Youth March for Integrated Schools
    - Sub-Series 6. Shop Correspondence, 1959
      - Groups of Shops, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - A, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - B, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - C, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - D, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - E-F, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - G, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - H, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - I-J-K, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - L, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - M, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - N-O, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - P-Q, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - R, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - S, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - T-V, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - W, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Sub-Series 7. Workers Correspondence, 1959
      - A-C, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - D-F, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - G-L, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - M-O, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - P-R, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - S-T-V, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - W-Z, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series B. Locals, 1959
    - Sub-Series 4. Form Letters, 1959
      - Local 64, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Local 80/85, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Local 88, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Local 150, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
    - Sub-Series 5. Notices to Mediation Boards, 1959
      - Local 48, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Local 61, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Local 64, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 15-21)
      - Local 80, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Local 85, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Local 88, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 24-27)
      - Local 150, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 28-32)
    - Sub-Series 7. Shop Correspondence, Local 64, 1959
      - A, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - B, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - C, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - D-E-F, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - G-H, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - I-J-K, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - L, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - M, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - N-O, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - P-Q-R - Russeks, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - S, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - T, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - U, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - W-Z, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Sub-Series 8. Workers Correspondence, 1959
      - A-B-C, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - D-E-F, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - G-H-I-J, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - K-L-M, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - N-O-P, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - Q-R-S, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - T-Z, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Summary of Communications, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 55)
        Concise descriptions of the various correspondence that has taken place within the union; the summaries list correspondence received that request response. The summaries report on the recommended action taken.
  - Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1960
    - Sub-Series 1. General Correspondence, 1960, 1960
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. - Chicago (1960) Jan.- May (Box 18, Folder 1)
        Financial statement; support of Sen. Murray and his poultry legislation bill resolution for the 20th General Convention; routine correspondence
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. - Chicago (1960) June-Dec. (Box 18, Folder 2)
        From Sam Burt to Patrick Gorman re proposed amendments to the By-laws in view of the Landrum-Griffin Labor Law; Swift & Company Strike
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. - Convention - Intl., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
        Minutes of Proceedings
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        Proposed International Constitutional amendment to Article X & New Pension Plan
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        Preconvention papers/correspondence; convention call; convention statement of membership
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. Convention, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        Womens Committee; invitations; ladies luncheon; fashion show; entertainment during convention; minutes of the pre-convention
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. - New York City, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        List of members interested in Bronx Cooperative Housing Development; routine correspondence
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. - (other locals), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Abbot & Adams, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        Co-op housing project; appraisal of cold storage plant to Sam Burt
      - Brochures - Booklets - Leaflets, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Burt, Sam (Testimonial Dinner), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
        5/14/60. Invitations, RSVP's; pre dinner arrangements
      - Burt, Sam (Testimonial Dinner), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        Contributions; speech; description of dinner activities; photos
      - Burt, Sam (Israel & Europe), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 14)
        Itinerary, correspondence
      - Butchers District Council, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
        Correspondence; Resolutions adopted at A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A.; convention; routine correspondence
      - Butchers District Council, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 17-20)
        Form letters; meeting notices; minutes
      - Butchers District Council, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        Miscellaneous; financial report of 1960 Labor Day Committee; list of newly adopted by-laws; Joseph Cohn "Meet the New VP" dinner; from Cammer & Shapiro re Landrum-Griffin registration & election requirements
      - Cammer & Shapiro, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        Advice on compliance with Landrum-Griffin Act Real Property Law; request for increased retainer; integration of Local 61 members into Local 64
      - Car Rentals, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        Use of organization owned automobiles
      - Cohn, Joseph Dinner - Program; invitations-rsvp's, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Completed contract renewal notifications, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
        List of expiring contracts for each local by month
      - A-B-C - Miscellaneous - General correspondence, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Finance Committee Letters, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 27)
        Members in arrears - Local 64
      - D-F - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Housing, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 29)
        Proposed limited profit housing company in Greenwich Village; using welfare & pension fund to alleviate housing shortage
      - Inter Office Correspondence, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Israel-Histadrut, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 31)
        Campaign news bulletin, booklet published by AFL-CIO "Ten Years of Progress" ...a report on Israel; publication by General Federation of Jewish Labor in Israel "Work"; Histadrut Foto News - published by National Committee for Labor Israel
      - G-I Miscellaneous Routine, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Liberal Party, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 33)
        Routine invitations, notices
      - Miscellaneous J-L, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 35)
        Gazzetta official della Repubblica Italiani; publication entirely in Italian 8/30/60; NLRB case - C&W Sewing Machine Attachment vs Gallina
      - Montreal Fur Workers, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 36)
        Speech by George Greenberg at the Montreal Fur Fashion Show; Arden Fur problems; agreement with Fur Manufacturers Guild
      - Misc. M-N-O, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Promotional Campaign, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 38)
        Continuation of 1959 Fur Info & Fashion Council promotion of furs; description of promotional activities; budget; Fur Topics - newspaper of the Fur Info and Fashion Council
      - Properties, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Reports, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 40)
        1959 reports for Joint Board, Local 48, 64, 80, 85 & 88 re major contracts, wage increases, etc.
      - Miscellaneous P-Q-R, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - I.F. Stone Weekly, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 42)
        An independent weekly published & edited by I.F. staff; political news
      - Tariff Commission Hearing, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 43)
        8/1/60; statement of Sam Burt before U.S. Tariff Commission "Peril Paint" investigation
      - Miscellaneous S-T-U, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 44)
        Benefits for U.S. Blindstitch Machine Corp. Employees. Routine
      - White Lake Lodge, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 45)
        To Rabbi Jacob Nislick for Cammer & Shapiro re late payments on mortgage
    - Sub-Series 2. Elections, 1960
      - Voting card eligibility; certification of elected members, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Sub-Series 3. Financial contributions, 1960
      - Contributions, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 47-48)
    - Sub-Series 4. Form letters, 1960
      - January - December, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 49-50)
    - Sub-Series 5. Organizer's Reports - Joint Board, 1960
      Daily reports on activities
      - November, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 51-52)
      - December, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 53-55)
    - Sub-Series 6. Shop Correspondence - Local Form Letters, 1960
      - Group of Shops, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - A, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - B, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - C, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - D, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - E-F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - G, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - H-I, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - J-K, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - L-M, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - N, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - P, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Q-R, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - S, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - T-V, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - W-Z, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Sub-Series 7. Worker Correspondence, 1960
      - A-B, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - C, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - D, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - E-G, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - H-J, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - K-L, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - M-N, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - P-R, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - S-T, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - U-Z, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series B. Locals, 1960
    - Sub-Series 2. Election Materials,, 1960
      - Local 48F Minutes of election committee results, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Local 61F Election material - questionnaire for nominees results, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Sample ballots - pre-election material; minutes of election committee meeting; notification of nomination, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Local 64 Election materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 30)
        Pre-election materials; minutes of membership meeting, 3/1/60
      - Local 64 Election, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 31)
        Nominations; questionnaire for nominees results
      - Local 64 Election - Notification of nominations, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 32-34)
        Minutes of elections committee, membership nominees & questionnaires; pre- election materials
      - Local 80 Election, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Local 80 Election - Notification of nomination results, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Local 85 Election, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 37)
        Pre-election materials; minutes of membership & elections committee meeting; nominations/questionnaire
      - Local 85 Election Materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 38)
        Notification of nominations results
      - Local 88F Election Materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 39)
        Notification of nomination membership meeting minutes
      - Local 88F Election Materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 40)
        Ballots; cards; questionnaire results
      - Local 150 Election Materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 41)
        Pre-election materials; minutes of membership/elections committee
      - Local 150 Election Materials, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 42)
        Nominations/questionnaires
      - Local 150 Elections, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 43)
        Notification of nominations
      - Local 150 Elections, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 44)
        Results
    - Sub-Series 4. Form letters, 1960
      - Local 48F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Local 61, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Local 64, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 47)
        January-March
      - Local 64, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 48)
        April-August
      - Local 64, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 49)
        September-December
      - Local 80F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - Local 85F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 51)
      - Local 88F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 52)
        February-April
      - Local 88F, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 53)
      - Local 150, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 54)
        January-April
      - Local 150, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 55)
        May-December
    - Sub-Series 5. Notices to Mediation Boards, 1960
      Contract termination notice to State & Federal Boards
      - Local 64, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Local 85, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Local 88, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Local 150, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
    - Sub-Series 6. Organizers Reports, 1960
      - Organizers Reports, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        Number of visits made by each organizer listed by month (January-December)
      - Organizers Reports, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 8-8a)
        January 1960. Organizers daily reports on shop visits; complaints adjusted; conferences with employers; arbitration hearings, etc.
      - February, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
      - March, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
      - April, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
      - May, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
      - June, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 17-18)
      - July, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
      - August, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
      - September, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
      - October, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
      - November, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Sub-Series 7. Shop Correspondence, Local 64, 1960
      - A-B-C, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - D-E-F, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - F, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - G-H-I, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - J-K-L, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - M, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - N, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - P-R, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 35)
        Russeks, 1960-61 re arbitration & violation of CB agreement, welfare fund and general correspondence
      - Russeks, January-April 1960 (Box 20, Folder 36)
        January -April
      - Russeks, May-July 1960 (Box 20, Folder 37)
        May-July
      - Russeks, September-December 1960 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Russeks, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - S - Shop Correspondence, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - T - Shop Correspondence, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - U-Z, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Sub-Series 8. Worker Correspondence, Local 64, 1960
      - Groups of Workers, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - A-B, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - C-D, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - E-F, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - G, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - H-J, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - K-L, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - M-N-O, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - P-R, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - S, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - T-Z, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 53)
      - Summary of Communications, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1961
    - Sub-Series 1. General Correspondence, 1961
      - A - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - AFL-CIO Film on Fur Industry, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        "Americans At Work" & Furriers, time listing and showings
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A., 1961 - Chicago (Jan.-April) (Box 21, Folder 3)
        Sam Burt to Thomas J. Lloyd on suggested merger between Local 80/85 & 88 & suggested name changes; letter urging locals to aid in caring for Cuban refugees; preparation for National Conference in Chicago; merger between 80 FL, 85 FL, 88 FL; new charter fo
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. (May-December 1961) Chicago (Box 21, Folder 4)
        Morris Cohen to Thomas J. Lloyd requesting strike sanction from international office memo dealing with Singer Sewing Machine; COPE funding
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. (notices-circular) Chicago, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
        Changes in retirement plan; increase in dues in order to stabilize the International Strike Benefits Fund; passage of minimum wage bill
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. (New York) 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
        General, routine correspondence
      - A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A. (other than NY/Chicago), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration - Herman A. Gray, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 8)
        Hearing involving above arbitrator & various employers; Chester Fasanelli; David Enleen & Archie Levitt
      - Auction Company Negotiations - 1961 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - B - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        To Paul Burt from Henry Foner re scholarship in memory of father
      - Basch - Crown-Monarch, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
        Difficulties in obtaining furs for good prices to Sam Burt from Crown Monarch
      - Burt, Sam - Condolences, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
        Cas de recherch; describes death of Burt; telegrams expressing sympathy; letters of condolences; newspaper clippings
      - Burt, Sam - Memorial Meeting, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 14)
        Speeches given by Brother Myer Klig, Lyndon Henry, George Stofsky, Irving Kaplan, Pat Gorman, Abe Feinglass; press releases
      - Butchers District Council correspondence (1961) (Box 21, Folder 15)
        Proposed by-laws/amendment (January-April); financial statements
      - Butchers District Council Correspondence, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        General routine correspondence; resolution supporting new Food Trades Vocational School
      - Butchers District Council Minutes, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Butchers District Council - Workshop, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 18)
        6/19/61. Agenda; pre-workshop information
      - C - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 19)
        General correspondence, requests for donations
      - C.R.A. Strike, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
        War stoppage report; request for strike sanction; union demands for contract renewal
      - Cammer & Shapiro, Esqs., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 21)
        With various parties re violations of NLRA; collective bargaining agreements; reliable attachment; NY Fur Cleaners Association